A Finding Aid to the LeRoy Neiman Papers, 1938-2005, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Project Files, 1949-2005, undated; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 20-39, 78-81; 20.2 linear feet)
  - Projects and Commissions, 1949-2005, undated; 3.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Robert F. Kennedy Pro Celebrity Tennis Tournament - Correspondence and Press, 1972-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Robert F. Kennedy Pro Celebrity Tennis Tournament - Programs, 1972-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Robert F. Kennedy Pro Celebrity Tennis Tournament - Programs, 1972-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Circle Galleries Solo Exhibitions, Los Angeles, Dallas, NYC, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Jack Nicklaus and Arnold Palmer, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Rotonda Superstars, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Ali vs. Frazier II, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Hawaii and Japan, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Saratoga Harness, 1969, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Gallery Mack, Seattle and Carmel, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Windsor Gallery Solo Exhibitions, Los Angeles, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Frank Sinatra at Carnegie Hall Poster, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Dinah! (Dinah Shore television show), 1974-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Royal Doulton Collectible Plates, 1974-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Leo Durocher, 1974-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Ali vs. Frazier III "The Thrilla in Manila,", 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Tampa Bay Rowdies Soccer, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - James Talcott, Inc., 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Miss World-USA Beauty Pageant, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Hess's Gallery Solo Exhibition, Allentown, PA, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Julius Erving, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - St. Paul Bicentennial, Minnesota Museum of Art Painting, 1974-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - St. Paul Bicentennial, Minnesota Museum of Art Painting, 1974-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Newport Jazz Festival, 1975-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 22)
      - Programs, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Press and Correspondence, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Rusty Staub, 1975-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Montreal Olympics, 1976-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Knoedler London Solo Exhibition, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Indianapolis Museum of Art Solo Exhibition, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Emerald Art Gallery Solo Exhibition, Coronado, CA, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Heit Galleries Solo Exhibition, Phoenix, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Kool Jazz Festival, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Etchings of LeRoy Neiman Booklet, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Sportsman's Park Mural, Chicago, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Burger King Promotion, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Sweden Exhibitions, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Malletmen Etching Certificate, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Lone Ranger, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Edward Fields, Inc, Carpet Tapestries, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Bowles/Hopkins Solo Exhibition, San Francisco, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Casa Grafica Solo Exhibition, Helsinki, Finland, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - St. Lawrence National Bank Solo Exhibition, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Cosmos Soccer, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Japan Trip, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - "Ball, Bat, and Glove," Spectrum Fine Art, New York, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Sculpture, 1977-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Neiman News, 1977-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Thurman Munson and Thurman Munson Awards, 1977-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Superbowl XII, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Sportsman's Ball, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Miss USA Pageant, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Ali vs. Spinks, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Gallery Mack Solo Exhibition, Seattle, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Elayne Galleries Solo Exhibition and P.J. Clarkes, Minneapolis, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Art Exchange Solo Exhibitions, Creve Coeur, MO, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Naismith Memorial Basketball Hall of Fame, 1978-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - University of Kentucky Wildcats, 1978-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - International Tennis Hall of Fame Group Exhibition, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Classic Leather Catalog Cover, 1978, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Bill Bradley, 1978-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Charlotte Chandler, 1978-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Hammer Graphics Gallery Solo Exhibition, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Drake Relays, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Race of the Year, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - AMF Soccer Equipment Promotion, 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Sports Commemorative Whiskey Decanter, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - F.X. McRory's Whiskey Bar, 1978-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 23)
      - Press and Publicity, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Photographs, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - New Jersey State Opera Ball Paintings, 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - New Jersey State Opera Ball Paintings, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Advertising Layouts, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Winter Olympics, Lake Placid, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Famous-Barr Olympic Benefit Solo Exhibition, St. Louis, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Ali vs. Holmes, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Egypt-Israeli Peace Treaty Painting, Peace Treaty, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Neiman's Restaurant and Lounge, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - L. Roy Papp, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Willie Stargell, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Caesar's Palace, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Adoption Guild Tennis Tournament, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Alan King Caesar's Palace Tennis Classic, 1980-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Duran vs. Leonard I, II, III, 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Rocky Films, 1981-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Harry's on Hanover Square, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Williams at Bat, 1980-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Roy Eaton, 1980-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Neiman/Warhol Exhibition at LAICA, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24)
      - Publicity, Press and Correspondence, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Essay Manuscripts, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - "Drawings by LeRoy Neiman," Oklahoma Art Center, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - "Drawings: A Retrospective" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "Rooster,", 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Hearns vs. Leonard, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Tribute to Joe Louis (Holmes vs. Spinks fight), 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Cities in Schools and Harlem Streets, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Miss Universe Pageant, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Charlie Cosmetics Promotion, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Nolan Ryan, 1981-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Stadium Tennis Billboard, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Great Irish Fair, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Caesar's Palace Grand Prix, 1981-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Turnberry Isle Yacht and Racquet Club Exhibitions, 1981-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Victor Awards, 1981-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - WNBC Traffic Helicopter, 1981-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Wayne Gretzky, 1981-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Figure Skating National Championships, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Million Dollar Strike, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - The Open Heart, circa 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Harrod's Gallery Solo Exhibition, London, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. America Pageant, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Gaylord Perry, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Holmes - Cooney Fight, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Ocean Club Condominiums, Atlantic City Promotion, 1982-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Pebble Beach Golf, 1982-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Morton's of Chicago, 1982-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Carousel Ball, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 25)
      - Correspondence, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Programs, 1982-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
      - Album, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Album, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Album, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Folies Bergere, Tropicana, Las Vegas, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 25)
      - Photos, Correspondence and Clippings, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Magazines, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - "Showstoppers" Group Exhibition at MCNY, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Miss Teen USA Pageant, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Volvo Masters Painting, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Tokyo Exhibition, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Ella in Flight, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - US Open, Oakmont, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Hanson Art Galleries Solo Exhibitions, New Orleans and Carmel, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Miss America Pageant, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Des Moines Ballet Commissions, 1983-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Julio Iglesias, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Arkansas Symphony Orchestra and Arkansas Wild Ducks, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - LeRoy Neiman Corvette, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Dallas Grand Prix, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26)
      - Press Kit and Correspondence, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Press and Magazines, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Harrah's Trump Plaza Opening, Atlantic City, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Beauty, the Beach, and the Bizarre, Cannes Film Festival Promotion, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - LeRoy Neiman Centennial Art Exhibition, Springfield, MA, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - 43rd Crosby National Pro-Am Golf Championship, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Los Angeles Olympics, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26)
      - Press, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Photographs, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Sarajevo, Winter Olympics, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - General Electric Phone Promotion, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Iona College Trustee Awards Dinner Dances, 1984-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - New York City Marathon, 1984-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 26)
      - Press and Correspondence, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Magazines, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Superbowl XIX, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - The Texas Longhorns, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Lady Liberty, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Center Art Galleries Exhibition, Hawaii, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - "The LeRoy Neiman Collection" Exhibition, Hammer Galleries, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - National Cowboy Hall of Fame, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Alexander Hotel Promotion, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Hagler vs. Hearns, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Lawrence Ross Galleries, 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - "Art", Group Exhibition at Area, New York, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - "American Masters of the 40s, 50s, and 60s," Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - March of Dimes' Gourmet Gala, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - The Toy Store Exhibitions and Promo, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Skoal Pinch Hitter of the Year, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Indianapolis 500, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - James Beard, 1985-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - St. Paul Winter Carnival Painting, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Arrow Shirts Promotion, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Goodwill Games Moscow, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Miss Asia Pageant, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - America II, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Nob Hill, Buena Vista and Bowles Hopkins Gallery, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Hanson Art Galleries Solo Exhibition, La Jolla, CA, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Peri-Reneth Gallery Solo Exhibition, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Sharp Copier Promotion, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - ASPCA, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Mike Tyson Portraits, 1986-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Millrose Games, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Art Aid, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - "LeRoy Neiman in Moscow" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Marlborough Galleries Exhibition, Boston, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Hanson Art Galleries Solo Exhibition, San Francisco Bay Area, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Bowles/Sorokko Galleries Solo Exhibitions, San Francisco ("Neiman's Neimans") and Beverly Hills, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Palm Springs Commemorative Coin, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - U.S. Savings Bonds Campaign, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Friars Club Exhibition, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Tretyakov Museum Solo Exhibition, Moscow, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Tokyo Exhibition, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Baird Jones' Group Exhibitions, New York, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Symphantasy, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Superbowl XXII painting In the Pocket, at Allyson Louis Gallery, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Fairfax Police Youth Club Soccer Tournament Poster, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Bob Hope Portrait, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Senatorial Candidate Peter Dawkins Poster, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Tyson vs. Spinks, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Postal Service Superbowl History Stamps, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - United Nations "Health in Sports" Stamps, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Golden Nugget Casino, Las Vegas, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Skip Singleton Tennis Books, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Superbowl XXIII Painting, Superplay, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Tour de Trump, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Mustang Ranch Brothel, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Johnny Bench, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Emerson Fittipaldi, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Frank Sinatra at Royal Albert Hall, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Caliente Race Track Exhibition and Painting, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Classic Moments LeRoy Neiman Watch Collection, Archival Resource Key (Box 28)
      - Correspondence, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Publicity, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Dyansen Gallery Playboy Collection Touring Exhibition, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Steiner & Young Galleries Exhibition, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Soft Paintings, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Gone with the Wind Perfume Promotion, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Midwest Museum of Art Exhibition, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Polo Lounge Debut at Bowles Sorokko Galleries, Beverly Hills, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - "A Salute to Central Park" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Anheuser Busch World Cup Soccer Poster, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Houston Film Fest, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Wine Country Film Festival, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - John Lennon Etching, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Dodgers Centennial, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Orlando Magic, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - '21' Club Painting, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Bay Area Baseball debut at Bowles Sorokko, San Francisco, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Gallery One Solo Exhibition, Denver, Colorado, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Merv Griffin's Resorts Casino Exhibition, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Denver Grand Prix, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Absolut Vodka Commission, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Kayo Joe Louis Boxing Card, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Philadelphia Spectrum Painting, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - The Shot Heard 'Round the World, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Miami Grand Prix, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco Series, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Tyson vs. Holyfield, 1991-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Topps Celebrity Trading Card, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Orr for the Defense, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - "Drawing New Conclusions," Art Institute of Chicago Group Exhibition, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Dyansen Gallery Solo Exhibition, Atlantic City, and The Beatles Serigraph, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - 'Wild Animals' and 'Art of Sport' Calendars, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Larry Bird, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Bill Walsh, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Billboard Magazine First Annual Billie Awards, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Falstaff Opera, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Iroquois Steeplechase, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Jackie Robinson Foundation, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Women's Basketball Hall of Fame, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - McGirt vs. Whitaker, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Call of the Wild, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - "Un Americain à Paris," Solo Exhibition, Galerie Marcel Bernheim, Paris, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Frank Sinatra Portraits for Duets and Duets II Albums, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 29)
      - Press, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence and Photographs, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Phil Rizzuto, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Winter Olympics, Lillehammer, Norway, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Superbowl XXVIII, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Absolut Vodka Advertisement, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Monaco Trip, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Howard Stern, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Saks Fifth Avenue Catalog, 1994-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 30)
      - Catalogs, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
      - Correspondence, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Mayor Giulianni and NYC Advisory Commission for Cultural Affairs, 1994-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Florida Gators, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Cadillac Hambletonian Harness Race Painting, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Universal Geneve Timepieces Promotion, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - OMTI LeRoy Neiman Opera Lab Theater, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 15)